Rehan Khan in Final Boss on Squares Today
in this video I am going to talk about
how to request ICICI Bank's NOC letter
online and get it. If we have
not received our NOC letter, then the previous
video we made was how to fold ICICI Bank
credit card online through mail.
So if you mail on the date on which you send the mail,
after sending the mail you get a
return from ICICI, then
wait for three days from that day. If you do
not get this letter, then the
ward number of customer care is given above, you can
call there from your registered number and confirm with them.
What happened to the NOC letter earlier?
If it gets resolved from there, then it is a very good
thing. Your problem gets solved, then it is a
good thing. If there is a problem from there also,
you feel that nothing is going to happen,
then the last way is that we will send an email
and then we will request our amphitheater. So
you also know how to send an email. I will
tell you guys by writing an email how to
write the mail and from where to write it, everything, so let's
know.  Let's look at the mobile screen and see
how to write the mail for the amphitheater.
See, friends, we get it and
in the mail, we have to write to the office. They also
tell you this. See, head service
quality ad bread icicibank.com
on this seat. See
customer.care at icicibank talk to me
2c. Now we will keep customer care.
After that, we are going to tell you how to write the mail for the NOC letter. So,
1 minute has been removed from here.
See, in this subject we will write NOC
request. Then below we will write the date, whatever the
date will be, on which date you will send the mail,
you will write that data. Then after that, ICICI
credit card, then below we will write To home 8
in on sir no
respectfully I am writing to come for
Close My credit card number. Here we will
cut our carats and write the number. Then further we will
write with name of credit card, we will
write your name as it is
immediately. Then after that we will come down. This is
also a request to please your
NOC for clearance and sandy.  To my
address, on the line below the address, you will
write the current address. If you want to order it at home or at the
office, you will
write the address of wherever you order it. On this, send
my email ID and here you will write your mail
ID and say send it to my home address
and also email me my Yantra
letter. Then after that you will write I am really
grateful for all the service I want you to receive and never had any complaint. All will be
clear till date. My cardinal is attached *
behind us. Your requirements are to cut your
credit card into two pieces and
after cutting it into two pieces, take a photo of it and
attach it to this mail.
Write warm regards and your name below and attach it.
You know, next to compose,
write the attached file from here. After attaching that photo, you will
send it from here, then
you will get a reply from there and very
soon you will get the NOC letter. You have seen that you
can request the NOC letter by mailing in this way. So
that's all for now, see you
with the next video and if you are new to our channel then
Subscribe to our channel,
like it and share it as much as possible so that
this message reaches those who want to close Quikr
and that's it, see you in the next video.